hmm I'm gonna start by saying if you get smart with me if you're not helpful I'm just gonna
block you because this is like a real thing okay so people are trying to so I okay I was told
that because of my hair texture I need to interlock I mean that I need to crochet lock
but I need to find out hold on I'm blocking this person um I need to find out if that's true
or if the palm roll will work because if I do palm roll how do I keep it staying DJ Johns shut up
I'm not playing in my head shut up anyways okay I am getting a crate a crochet needle
but then I hear different things some people are like well if you have the crochet needle
it kind of doesn't really allow your lock to like really lock no you don't just have to keep the
maintenance up hold on we have the same fine curly hair either will work but the crochet needle will
secure it more and protect your hairline over time so crochet hook sorry someone said needle
I wouldn't be doing this if I had a hairdresser I wouldn't literally be on Instagram asking for
locks advice if I had a hairdresser so palm roll doesn't gather all the hair and can thin out your
locks crocheting is better palm rolling is good but don't do it too frequently I'm not doing that
I'm not doing a whole new weekly hair routine I'm not doing that the whole point of me having locks is
so I don't need to do a whole weekly routine and all type of thing I'm reading is there a version of
life where I just like interlock just around the halo and then I palm roll the rest no one is saying
dreads no one here is saying dreads we're saying locks right Zakiya that makes sense what is the
difference between interlock and crochet I'm gonna look up the three-point method I thought I already
wrote it down when you said it I don't know where Somerset New Jersey is I'm in Nyack the reality is
that I'm not paying people all of this money no more like I'm just not doing it I'm not I I'm an
overly generous person I've been shit on now by two locks two lotticians two the first one who did my
original locks and fucked me over crazy she ruined my hair it was a whole thing and then this one I thought
was my friend and then she lost her fucking mind because she tried to switch up and I was like
I feel like you're switching up and then she became a narcissist well she was a narcissist the whole time
I just didn't know talking to me about Philadelphia I don't live in Philadelphia I'm not going to
Brooklyn I'm not going to Baltimore I'm not going to Maryland I don't understand why people are telling
me about other states I just I don't understand and I don't know what oil do I don't I don't use oil
I don't know necessarily how that even applies to what I'm trying to figure out right now I got people
telling me about yeah you know I wish you could come to Cincinnati what are you talking about sorry
one second someone just said Philly's not that far Philly's far Philly's far I'm looking crazy I
didn't I didn't think you were serious but no I feel you didn't think I was serious you asked
that's it I didn't even have a lot of time I have a call at 8 30 but I'm gonna now you got a call right
now stop stop um you going through it right now with this hair because it's been crazy for a while
now and I got left out in the cold so now I'm like okay yeah I also have things I need to do where my
hair needs to be in a better state fair um seeing it right now I think while you're trying to figure
out you can palm roll to get it where you where you want to get it to be presentable or a presentation
and figure out a style or either whether it's two strand twist or something like that so that you can
hold the hold whatever retwisting method you're doing a bit longer while you figure out what you want
to do so whether that's what do you mean while I figure out what I want to do in terms of do you want
to use an interlocking method do you want to continue so interlocking is you're essentially
I don't know how to explain it is it like you're pulling the lock through the hole yes you're
pulling a lock through the hole what they're saying in a three-point turn is like you're doing it in a
cross type shape and that's going to hold and that's essentially going to hold it close as close
to your root as possible but I feel like that just feels like it would strain on my like I feel
like my hair is not it depends on your texture it depends on your texture because like I went to
someone today and she did that and I was like no
she did one you're like that's too much tension and it is for some folks that is too much tension
and it might cause it might cause the pulling then thinning the lock long term that's why I was
talking about if you want to maintain the integrity of like how thick the lock is you have to decide
how you want it to look over time and so if you want them to be nice and thick like I like how they
look I want them to look like that you want them to keep looking like that which is which they look
good and so I guess I'd my advice seeing it right now and if you do have something coming up you can go
for you can try a palm roll so I did do that the other day I had to host an event and I palm rolled
and it did look cute but within two days that's so that's why I mentioned if you want to palm roll
in a style palm roll into a style that's going to let it hold a little bit longer okay so that will
keep the palm roll because if you if you just palm roll and then let it loose it's yes it's going to
unravel got it see that people weren't weren't really saying that they was like palm roll and
live your life no you're saying you're saying palm roll palm roll and then style so either whether
you're doing barrel like barrel into a bun or where are you from wait wait where are you from
like where I'm Jamaican but right now okay I heard barrel barrel so you can have four syllables okay
so you can you can you can palm roll into a barrel like either down or up I don't I don't want you to
have too much tension if you notice that if you want to like maintain your edges but you palm roll
into a style and that will help to hold whatever retwist and style you're doing
if you don't want it to just go away and you know my last question because I know you have to go
when you're just watching my hair from here you would say that a crochet is the best right
no I actually don't even think you have enough new growth to to to justify to just to justify it
new growth like you because I want you to keep I want you to keep thick locks and it doesn't matter
what you're doing to retwist your hair the more that you're that you're doing it it's going to
thin out your lock over time
so you're saying like even just these baby hairs here yeah that's you're saying just just live a
naughty dread life you have to live a naughty dread life for some time to to really make to get a good
thick lock so even though up here is a completely I'm not completely but you see how my texture here
is like you see how massa is coming through I see I see I see it I see it it's fine it's it could
frizz a bit but nothing that a good gel and tie down is not gonna fix should I be putting anything
on it to help it does your hair build up with product like do you notice that you have build up
or anything no it doesn't really hold so then that's so that's good so then you so then you can
tolerate some products something that you feel really comfortable with and like gel them down
mousse them down and tie it down and go watch your business no I mean like um like do I need to put
like beeswax or anything no no no beeswax no beeswax okay okay beeswax no beeswax so even though my hair
is soft yes I don't need to I just so basically what you're saying is just juices and berries like
personally yeah you know it doesn't have to be like that but personally juices berries
juices and berries just because you want to think about it like if you want to keep them a long time
juices and berries and oil but you can you can use stuff you can totally use stuff there's a lot
there's a lot out there that's not do you have any suggestions of products that you think yeah
there's um there's like a there's a black I think there's there's like a black tub I don't know
if maybe somebody's familiar with it and it's like black and red black and white writing there's like
a flower on it I can't think of the name right now um and I'm not a loctician I've just have
lost for like going on nine years now but um I think you guys I can't I can't see comments I just
see like myself but because Instagram is shadow banning me so they don't let people see the
comments oh for three years yeah
so well thank you for your input I guess I'm gonna this is gonna be me bringing people with
locks and locticians up to get insight so thank you have fun with them they look great enjoy them
love your hair love you bye
bye Westchester
okay um okay Sid you got all the mouth in the chat so take take the bonnet off
get a light on
y'all be in the chat
and then when I bring you live
sure
when I bring you live though y'all be like oh I think this is gonna go live
listen I didn't know it was really gonna come through I'm sitting here in the van and I'm
listening to the lovely sister give you some advice but I wanted to
yeah
you know
so tap in I'm taking multiple advice like I'm not just going to one source you
and listen you hit me with an all caps saying I'm true to this and so I said oh well let me get my
notebook out absolutely absolutely I am going to give you the best advice you'll ever hear
um when you when you're alone with your hair
left your hair alone I know it feels like uh it's messy it's wispy it's going everywhere it's doing all
the things right
I feel like I look a mess
you do not you look beautiful you look beautiful and I think that you have you have a similar texture
to my own um it's a softer texture um it's a masa texture we have a combo of masa and africa
happening
absolutely absolutely but it's still a texture that is willing to lock up um with the proper
maintenance and care um so I don't recommend crocheting for your hair simply because your
hair is a little bit softer and you also um you didn't start that way so you kind of want to
keep I did start with a crochet you did you did yes okay so if you started with a crochet I always
recommend continue to go with what you've been going with it doesn't look like it because it
you know it's not fresh or whatever but you know no no shade sis no shade um but if that's what you
started with I recommend continuing that because if you switch up methods um it'll leave a little
demarcation in your locks mostly if you switch over to interlocking now if you go over to palm
rolling and you decide to stick with that that's not using a tool that's not knotting your hair
so it won't leave any type of demarcation but what I think your experience is um what you're
experiencing excuse me um just you have a softer texture hair and as your hair is growing out from
your maintenance it feels like it may be growing away from the lock and what you want it to do is to
grow into the lock um I specialize in palm rolling I do do offer crochet retwist um but I scream palm
rolled to the death of me you know I mean because I just feel as though a retwist is just strictly
maintenance it is not to help your hair last longer it is not a style it is simply retwisting
your hair so you're pulling that hair into the shaft and you're ensuring that it grows that way
so you have like a cylinder shape lock that's all a retwist is it's not meant to last long especially
if you have a softer texture like ours my retwist lasts maybe three to four days so I typically
correct and I typically I get my hair done exactly you I as the sister was saying before I definitely
think that you should style it I believe that you should style it in some form and you know and
listen if if you don't want to style it my good sis you might just have to be okay with a little
little bump and frizz now I will say I recommend I told I don't know if you saw but I am located
in North Jersey um I recommend you come have a seat in my chair and you try my retwist how much do you
charge for a retwist a hundred and ten dollars and that's for a crochet because I'm not paying
a hundred and ten dollars for something that lasts four days oh yeah yeah no so if you want a crochet
retwist that is going to be 200 but that is including your shampoo your conditioning your whatever
I'll also put you on to some good products um as far as oiling your scalp because I don't recommend
doing anything to your hair outside of um your appointments other than oiling your scalp maybe
once or twice a week that's really it you don't need the beeswax you don't need the it's all right
baby it's all right that's all right it look good to me I can't know it's not about it not looking good
as much as it it's not locking okay okay that's my concern is that like you got the lock but it is
but it is locking because you can see you have your hair like underneath that little bit of new
growth it's locking it's locking that's just new growth and I think that people get a little bit
concerned when the hair feels like it's growing away from the lock but once you get it maintained
it's it's coming right back it's just a little frizz so you're saying that there's a lock under there
yes you like you feel the little bud like it feels like it feels a little soft right but it's budding
that that's that's basically like if you were to start your hair from like little little minis as it
grows out it'll start to feel like it's budding before it actually becomes super firm you know so
it's locking up your hair is locking up I just think that you know the frizz is it's what throwing
it's throwing you off yeah people with our texture we don't feel like our hair is like I've had my hair
locked now for I've been locked since 2013 so 16 years my hair doesn't look super long because it's
curled but it comes down a little bit above my waistline and I've had it hold on one second
no activator stop please like y'all be in this chat and I want you to envision if I'm having a
conversation somebody and you're standing next to me yelling at me that's what it's like when y'all be
in the chat being redundant after I've already addressed your point and you then hit me with
the all caps like my autism cannot take all that okay I can't shit it was too much for you it was too
much for you sis I'm just like y'all give my girl a break y'all give my girl a break she's trying to
absorb all this information give her give her a second I really am because I just want to make
sure I'm not making a mistake because the first time that I got locks the woman lied to me the first
person who like put locks in my hair lied to me she was like oh I'm gonna do like hair around your
lock and there's gonna be a lock inside she said oh lord and there and your hair is gonna lock
inside it and I was like okay you're trusting her to guide you in the right direction and she ruined
my hair and I looked a fucking mess absolutely so oh my god so then the the loctician who took over
she was like we're gonna get you right we're gonna crochet we're gonna put some color on the end
so like this is all all the dark brown is me but even I didn't want to be because she ended up
wrapping the blonde up yeah I didn't want to I never asked anybody are those real locks but I did want
to ask you know do you have like extensions on the end like no so the extensions are like
at this point not really because basically it's like it's grown out yes it's grown out and so she
would like kind of bring it up just to keep the ombre okay I did the same thing for my mom I
installed her locks maybe four or five years ago and hers are they've all dropped out um and her
texture is even closer to yours uh so I absolutely understand exactly what you're going through um like
I said the crochet maintenance it does last longer than um a natural retwist it will last you longer
um but as your hair like I said it grows out we have a softer wispier texture especially around
this hairline that's gonna appear like yeah that's gonna appear like I need you to understand that
this hairline has been plaguing me girl since the 1900s okay girl trust me I do because I see our skin
colors and we have been we've had a playground halo for life I need y'all to understand because this is
my this is my daddy up here okay okay okay my best friend gets on me because all of this just be
sticking out the bonnet she like girl cover it please it don't cover it don't cover my father this
is the black american father here and then back here is like some caribbean mixy mixy and then back
here is the actual slaves in the caribbean like listen we listen we in the same boat my my dad's
uh side of the film I'm guyanese so I got a little bit of you know it's like a little bit of that
guyanese gold right here right here same same same my grandmother rest in peace to lucille
2022 she wore this for the past 50 years I don't take this off I don't take this off yeah but that
was my girl that was my girl um but I I understand I understand my dear and I am here for you if you
need me so you're in so someone asked do I want my hair to look like salon locks and here's the thing
I don't want my hair to look like salon locks I just want to make sure I'm caring for my locks
properly absolutely that's really what this is about like I started to feel like yeah like I'm
just like damn I'm am I because because I've been going every quarter for the past two years so I'm
just like well you know if that's if I'm not doing that am I doing it wrong no no you're not doing it
wrong so I do want to come and at least get because the other part of it is that there's like lock
maintenance and like lock lock teaching right like when I when I had natural hair that was just
you know my curly hair I never was really taught how to like care for it until I went to Dickie at
hair rules I like did a show on MTV and like they had like sent us to him and he cut the shit out of
my hair and I cried in the chair but then we became best friends that's typically how it goes you're like
oh that needed to happen that needed to happen it's okay because he brought me to health
yeah absolutely and then he taught me how to care for my hair like for natural hair you know because
they always tell you like oh you shouldn't wash your hair and he like multiple times a week and
he was like what like black women please put water on your hair please right right so I'm now in that
I always I always say the the best rule of thumb is do what you think is best and when I say that I
mean do research I do mean like you said you're getting multiple opinions and whatever sounds like
it may work for your hair because there's not a one size fit yeah all when it comes to locks when it
comes to natural hair when it comes to black women's hair in general we all have different
types of textures um and sometimes people they can't control what happens to their hair you know
people are taking different medications people are right you know they're going through things
you're getting older so your hair changes so the advice that you receive that's going to change as
well yeah um so I'm a firm believer and you know like you said gather all the facts and do what you
think is best for you but I would love for you to you know come sit down talk with me me give you a
little bit of consult um I am also a traveling loctician I currently live um in Richmond Virginia
but I work in New Jersey 10 days out of the month um I worked there the last 10 days of the month and
I've been doing that for the past year you can ask my clients I'm very consistent I will never leave you
hanging it's a train right away I still have family in Jersey so I am here to help you whenever you need
me if you need me tomorrow evening I'm there for you so you just let me know I do want to I do want to
I'll follow you so that we can dm because when you're here in Jersey I'll come see you like
essentially um the the other question I have is that I've started swimming more just as a part of
my wellness regimen okay and you know it's kind of like okay is there a particular like shampoo or
conditioner that would be like better for locks right like is there a is there an after swim I mean
the place where I go has like the lowest amount of chlorine possible like okay so it's not like a um
crazy amount of chlorine because I was at the YMCA but then I got in the fight with the um
with the aquatic director Marcus he can go fuck himself so aquatic director I'm crying he must
stand up he he wasn't hip sis but you know you know what it is it's that niggas niggas get a title
it's not even niggas people get a title and they just feel like I'm about to room it blows their like
whoo like hold on we still we still people right we still you have on a you have on a black and white
camouflage do rag so we should do my hair oh my bad my bad so this new place where I'm going though
it's like a holistic place like it's very like very well cared for like the water is ionized you
have to wear a swim cap um but I am also just like okay yes I do wash my hair with um alapia which is
like shea butter um conditioner so I use like a really like positive product but I don't know if
it's like bad this is gonna sound cool this is gonna sound silly because I don't really know if
it sounds if this is making sense but because of the texture of my hair does swimming often make it
harder for it to lock no no it does not for the simple fact that your hair is already locked I want
you to ingrain it like it's already locked your hair is already locked babe you know in my mind
in my mind it's like this is locked and then this is my hair no babe your hair is already locked that's
new growth that you're worrying about so none of those things are affecting the ability of your hair
being locked that you only worry about that when you're in the beginning stages and you have no firmness
to your locks then constant water on it that would do something different to your locks you could be out
there swimming with no cap on if you wanted to it would not affect the way your hair is locking up
because like you said most of that stuff already grew up this is you you're already locked this has
been since September 2024 you're already locked babe you're already locked can I tell you a quick
story yes you can I'm here two stories y'all so I was in Grenada about a month ago okay and I went
to um there's a Rasta that has like a fruit stand but then when I went to the Rasta's fruit stand he
wasn't there but of course the fruit was still there so then I was like okay well I'm gonna wait
for him so then there was a chair so I went and sat in the chair so I sat there and I waited but
then he didn't come and then a guy walked by and he was like you know Rasta coming he coming he coming
so I didn't say okay I'll wait a little longer he never came so then I was like I just gonna get I
gonna leave him some money and I'm gonna take my cocoa and my mango and go so I did that but then I came
back later to see if he was there and I asked him you know hey I left your money but I want to know
if I left the right amount because I left you 7 EC and I don't know if that was enough he told you
know the teeth the money you know the tickets they take the money the people you know they take the
money and I was like what and he said yeah because someone had told me a Rasta woman was sitting here
waiting for you listen listen what what you say what you say Rasta woman yeah yeah Rasta woman thing
and I was like today last week I went to not even last week the other day I went to the Jamaican spot
and so when I was I was waiting in line it was my turn the brother came and he was like um he said
and I was like so but then I was like you know I said you know I'm lost but I'm not a Rastafarian
and he was like eh eh but Rasta is just love yeah so if you have love you're a Rasta you have love and
I was like yes I mean I'm love head to toe and he was like well then you're a Rasta man I said
I'm trying to tell you and it's such a beautiful feeling and um I'm sure you've experienced this before
us being of a a lighter skin you know what I'm saying like I feel like or I felt like coming up
you know I'm not as or but with my locks they make me feel so much more blacker than I appear and I
love that because growing up in North Jersey you know you have a lot of West Indians you have a lot
of so when they see you it's like they're like bless bless bless and you're like bless Rasta man you
know what I mean so like girl I feel you I feel you I feel you I feel you and I love that you
experienced that because I want you to keep that at the forefront of your mind when you see these
little wispy like girl that's a little that's a little edge little edge ain't nothing wrong and you
know for me a lot of times I know my hair is gonna do that that's why I wear curls a lot sometimes I get
my hair rolled with the curls and don't even retwist my roots because I don't mind the little poop as it
as it goes on your length is gonna kind of take away from that but I don't like it's gonna take
away from you feeling about the the wispies but I kind of like now that it appears that way because
it makes it appear a little bit thicker and not as scalpy because I don't know if you experience that
once you get a crochet reach like you're all scalp you're all scalp and it's cool for it to be neat
and stuff but like I like being super super scalpy anymore you know um and I believe you're right you're
right I mean it's very healthy dread I mean I feel you know I definitely feel as though um I'm coming
from the bush I'm a cutlass yeah you know I I feel very like I'm on the island and I have to go back
to Grenada soon so but you know but this this nigga right here I'm crying this this nigga right here though
listen I got a couple of them niggas okay okay a couple of them like is this a bang I'm like that
bang yeah definitely a bang we got we got like this is the curtain we got matching bang yes these are
the curtains that the young girls be doing with the um with the gel I don't do that I don't do the
edges no I refuse I'm not doing that when I get my hair done I pull that thing right back right back
into that junk and that's it ain't no swooping no extra that go right into the twist and it's
gonna pop out a couple days later and so have you and thank y'all the comments for giving me a lot of
they're like be free girl and I think that's I think that's the misconception nowadays when it comes
to lock simply because everything is so aesthetic yeah everybody got the nice parts everybody got
the styles the updo's the you know where we come from you know that ain't you know what I mean
right right right it's nice it's nice don't get and it's nice to do sometimes but what you have is
nicer it's beautiful it's you it's it's it's of you you know what I mean like and it's nothing more
beautiful than that yeah well this is this is very helpful because again my biggest fear was like
are you doing something wrong like is it is it unlocking and now no you got you know you're not
doing anything wrong you know because I don't want to have Massa up here and then and Marley down
here I don't want Marley here and Massa here I don't want it listen Massa's gonna grow into Marley
that that's what that's doing that's what that's all that's doing you're not doing anything wrong
in fact your locks look wonderful they look wonderful thank you they do um do you have any
suggestions and also just like regular maintenance of like the lock themselves like oils I should be
putting on them or anything so the lock itself I recommend whatever you put on your scalp so I make
an oil as well but I'm not a gatekeeper it's literally a couple essential oils I recommend put in a
bottle black casserole jojoba oil coconut oil almond oil and you could do a little bit of rosemary or
lavender for a little bit of scent because those are strong oils black casserole jojoba one more time
black caster jojoba almond oil what did I say rosemary rosemary okay and then and so you can you can
mix that in a bottle right coconut oil coconut oil coconut oil yes and you said rosemary if I want
to put a for a little bit of scent but the rosemary also helps um you know with the moisturizing
because the guy in here activation that threw me off he kept saying rosemary okay yeah yeah yeah like
you can put that in there as well um but what I recommend you mix that up in a little bottle and you
focus on your scalp your scalp is where your hair is growing from though that's those are your roots
those are your follicles that's what you need to treat you know when you put oil on your scalp you
want to massage it in your fingertips and massage it in because you want to stimulate your roots in
school they told us like you want to talk to your roots and say hey you're alive down there I'm just
feeding you wake up um you know I'm feeding you the ends of your hair I hate to call them dead ends but
essentially they've already grown out right so you don't want to focus so much on the care of your ends
because if you put too much oil or product it'll cause build up and everything will get stuck to
your locks you'll have lint all in the back of your locks from having oil like you know like I'm
if you inspect your back row nine times out of ten you have some lint in there like you can feel it
you can see it but it just comes from wearing sweaters and hoodies and it makes it worse when
you have oil or products on your actual locks so as long as you stimulate these roots here you know
you can spray a little something on there for a little shine if you want to look a shine something
like that but stimulate your roots everything is coming from your roots you want to be treating
your roots the hair itself that's what's growing out if you think about it the hair that's here
was once here right so if you treat it while it's up here it's going to get down here but you got to
start up here so so people were saying that you know I should put rose water first just to I guess
as like a toner so I don't know too much as time is going on people have been using the rose water
water itself is fine water opens up that shaft um so you can spray that on like lightly mist it
are you from philadelphia I grew up in the ewing trenton area that might be where that's coming from
water yeah water oh I'm crying I was like water ice okay yeah yeah yeah got it so I think that's
where that's coming from you know we're right across the bridge over there yeah um but um okay
now somebody here's like rose water is overrated you know what's fascinating about the comments y'all
y'all are so like everyone has very strong opinions I might have been one of them you were that's why
I was like come on in like let's um and then someone said rose water is traditional to use
the skin and hair in Palestine so then I'm using the rose water so okay so this has been super dupes
helpful um hold um so happy for that so happy for that I had you said what I had to take my
bonnet off for you I know you're watching the rookie all my friends have been tagging me in your post
and I've been talking like speaking it into existence like I'm going to run into somebody
of status because you are of status to me that is going to let me showcase my talent and even you
know even if it doesn't go beyond here I feel as though you gave me that voice this time to do that
so I appreciate you much for that well thank you and thank you for you know listen it's all about
preparation so absolutely but you you were you were prepared for the opportunity and you took the
bonnet off and said let's get into it now yes so um I will follow you and um thank you so much and
to everybody on here they've also been thanking you because you know this is this is how we've always
done our hair like we share we exchange you know there's information there's knowledge etc
joe spiff said he's recorded it he got you uh joe shout out to joe because we grew up in the same
church you know i'm saying lucille retting my counts camp counselor and my love and he's super
into natural hair and he has an oil that y'all might want to check out too so uh much love to joe spiff
thank you baby and thank you have a good night put you on it back up thank y'all so much you know
because i'm the type of gal that's like i fixate that's part of my autism i fixate so it's like
so this has made me very helpful hey danny um i'm over here making a song for my children's show
that i'm putting together she's gonna have songs for every episode so i'm writing a song right now
about immigrants um and uh if you all want to hear the beat this is this is this is the beat
but i have i produced the beat today but i haven't okay here you go so that's i uh i produced that
today so i'm still in the process of um writing the song so so far the song is um i'm not from where you
are from and that's okay my grandma's food wait i'm not from where you are from and that's okay
my grandma's food and your grandma's food wait my grandma's food and your grandma's don't taste the
same we have different customs and holidays but we should learn how to pronounce each other's names
because this whole world is made of people and places with love we embrace each other's cultures
wherever we go we carry our family their love is within our history stories it's for the kids y'all
it's for the kids that's why i'm singing it like that it's for the kids
so that is coming soon um
i'm just trying to keep my my spirits up all right oh stew when i mean it's coming out in like
july i have to i mean if the world is still standing um but um
i'm you know we start shooting next week so i mean the whole i also want to make sure that like
it's the kind of music that parents will learn from as well and yeah that's really like i love
that i'm affirmed i'm affirmed by a teacher y'all um i want parents to be also i want i like the music
can't be a joke you feel me so like the music needs to be top quality and kids deserve good music
like kids deserve good music like it doesn't need to be like like don't get me wrong like the babies
there's a particular type of music for the babies however like our kids that are like four and up now
they are one oh i've been shadow band for three years they are advanced and they are
neurodivergent they're like all these things you know so we need to meet them where they are
we need to meet them where they are like it doesn't need to be
basic it can be simple it doesn't need to be basic and you know um you know for teens
to be quite honest like i feel like teens are listening to teens always want to listen to music
that's older than them so i want to make music also that teens want to listen to but that grown-ups
do as well so i'm working on two things right now um and to be quite honest this is really fascinating
because i've never experienced this before but like i'll be like working on music and then i'll have
this like it's like a monkey on my shoulder like you're supposed to be doing something else and then
when i think about it i'm like what am i supposed to be doing and then i realized like bitch this is
what you're doing now this is what you're doing so like so uh thank y'all for giving me great advice
on the locks and encouragement and someone said i feel i look like i feel lighter you're so right
because i genuinely was like am i fucking up so to know that i'm not fucking up
great so shout out to the sisters that joined tonight that took their time and shared their
knowledge and information uh really appreciate that and i love that she had said like i don't
gatekeep that's the part for me that i do not do that nonsense the gatekeeping is crazy i know people
will ask me about like my lipstick the reason why i don't tell y'all the brand names of things
is because they did not pay me to endorse their brands no that's not gatekeeping that's me like
not being willing to be their billboard um but uh i've been needing a lot of encouragement i'm an
only child so thank y'all for the encouragement all right thank y'all for the encouragement nola always
got encouragement for me so thank you um and you all have a good night i'm gonna finish this song for
the for the kiddos muah